<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on Kuba Maria Mazurkiewicz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on Kuba Maria Mazurkiewicz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>W–E: Life Between West and East</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/art/we/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/art/we/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A chance visit to a popular fast food restaurant prompted me to reflect on my place in the world and how it has changed over the last thirty years. In the 1990s, we lived in Poland between the West and the East. Right now, it seems like we are somewhere else, but sometimes we go back there. You can read about this in the comic zine &lt;em&gt;W–E: Life between West and East&lt;/em&gt;, published and printed on a Risograph by Oficyna Peryferie.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-Space Sightseeing Trip</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/art/time-spacesightseeingtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/art/time-spacesightseeingtrip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Guide &lt;em&gt;Czasoprzestrzenna Podróż Krajoznawcza. Okolice Baranowa&lt;/em&gt; [Time-Space Sightseeing Trip: The Baranów Area] is the result of a research project focused on the site where Poland’s Central Communication Port is planned to be built. The publication premiered on July 19, 2025, at Pracownia Wschodnia in Warsaw during the closing event of the exhibition &lt;em&gt;Conceptual Future Tense: The CPK and Its Environs&lt;/em&gt;. The book is the third volume in the Regional Explorations Notebooks series by Dar Dobryszyc. It is available for purchase from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dardobryszyc.pl/sklep/mazurkiewicz-red-czasoprzestrzenna-podroz-krajoznawcza/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;publisher’s online store&lt;/a&gt; (in Polish only).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conceptual Future Tense</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/art/conceptualfuturetense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/art/conceptualfuturetense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conceptual Future Tense: The CPK and Its Environs&lt;/em&gt; was the culmination of several years of artistic research. The exhibition ran at Pracownia Wschodnia gallery in Warsaw from June 18 to July 21, 2025. As part of the artistic and curatorial collective behind the project (whose other members were Małgorzata Gurowska, Piotr Puldzian Płucienniczak, Anna Siekierska, and Agata Szydłowska), I contributed to both the research and the exhibition’s final form. One of elements of the project is also the publication &lt;em&gt;Czasoprzestrzenna Podróż Krajoznawcza. Okolice Baranowa&lt;/em&gt; [Time-Space Sightseeing Trip: The Baranów Area].&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samples of Alternative Death Symbols</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/art/samples-of-alternative-death-symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/art/samples-of-alternative-death-symbols/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A funeral is a highly conventionalised ritual. The nature of the ceremony often does not correspond to the lifestyle of the deceased. We lack death styles that correlate with our lifestyles. One small step towards the individualisation of funeral rituals is this set of alternative symbols of death and mourning. The book contains a solid collection of them, some of which are accompanied by commentary from invited relatives and friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
